{
    "Instructors": [
        {
            "CreatedCourses": ["C3981"],
            "role": "Instructor",
            "userId": "2870",
            "email": "f@gmail.com",
            "passwordHash": "ef797c8118f02dfb649607dd5d3f8c7623048c9c063d532cc95c5ed7a898a64f",
            "username": "farah"
        },
        {
            "CreatedCourses": [
                "C3221",
                "C7102"
            ],
            "role": "Instructor",
            "userId": "3926",
            "email": "yasmin2@gmail.com",
            "passwordHash": "3b0bbbb98aa865230f2d6979835302ca0bfbe94463489b1f28e81145d1d505fa",
            "username": "yasmin"
        }
    ],
    "Students": [
        {
            "Progress": [{
                "certificate": {
                    "studentId": "4522",
                    "certificateId": "CER4959",
                    "issueDate": "2025-11-23",
                    "courseId": "C3981"
                },
                "lessonQuizs": [
                    {
                        "quiz": {
                            "studentScores": [],
                            "studentAttempts": 0,
                            "questions": [
                                {
                                    "options": [
                                        "a",
                                        "c",
                                        "sd",
                                        "as"
                                    ],
                                    "correctAnswer": "a",
                                    "questionText": "Enter question 1 here"
                                },
                                {
                                    "options": [
                                        "sa",
                                        "sd",
                                        "das",
                                        "das"
                                    ],
                                    "correctAnswer": "sa",
                                    "questionText": "Enter question 2 here"
                                },
                                {
                                    "options": [
                                        "ds",
                                        "sd",
                                        "sd",
                                        "sd"
                                    ],
                                    "correctAnswer": "ds",
                                    "questionText": "Enter question 3 here"
                                },
                                {
                                    "options": [
                                        "ds",
                                        "dsf",
                                        "df",
                                        "dff"
                                    ],
                                    "correctAnswer": "ds",
                                    "questionText": "Enter question 4 here"
                                },
                                {
                                    "options": [
                                        "sdf",
                                        "vf",
                                        "fr",
                                        "rg"
                                    ],
                                    "correctAnswer": "sdf",
                                    "questionText": "Enter question 5 here"
                                }
                            ],
                            "QuizId": "Q5744_L0471",
                            "passed": false
                        },
                        "lessonId": "L0471",
                        "completed": false
                    },
                    {
                        "quiz": {
                            "studentScores": [5],
                            "studentAttempts": 1,
                            "questions": [
                                {
                                    "options": [
                                        "qew",
                                        "eqwe",
                                        "de",
                                        "eds"
                                    ],
                                    "correctAnswer": "eqwe",
                                    "questionText": "Enter question 1 here"
                                },
                                {
                                    "options": [
                                        "fe",
                                        "fef",
                                        "sef",
                                        "fg"
                                    ],
                                    "correctAnswer": "sef",
                                    "questionText": "Enter question 2 here"
                                },
                                {
                                    "options": [
                                        "hfh",
                                        "fhg",
                                        "hg",
                                        "d"
                                    ],
                                    "correctAnswer": "fhg",
                                    "questionText": "Enter question 3 here"
                                },
                                {
                                    "options": [
                                        "ht",
                                        "h n",
                                        "tn",
                                        "fth"
                                    ],
                                    "correctAnswer": "tn",
                                    "questionText": "Enter question 4 here"
                                },
                                {
                                    "options": [
                                        "h",
                                        "hf",
                                        "fd",
                                        "df"
                                    ],
                                    "correctAnswer": "hf",
                                    "questionText": "Enter question 5 here"
                                }
                            ],
                            "QuizId": "Q8984_L1429",
                            "passed": true
                        },
                        "lessonId": "L1429",
                        "completed": true
                    }
                ],
                "completed": true,
                "courseId": "C3981"
            }],
            "role": "Student",
            "userId": "4522",
            "EnrolledCourses": ["C3981"],
            "email": "f1@gmail.com",
            "passwordHash": "ef797c8118f02dfb649607dd5d3f8c7623048c9c063d532cc95c5ed7a898a64f",
            "username": "farah"
        },
        {
            "Progress": [
                {
                    "certificate": {
                        "studentId": "6209",
                        "certificateId": "CER3850",
                        "issueDate": "2025-11-23",
                        "courseId": "C3981"
                    },
                    "lessonQuizs": [
                        {
                            "quiz": {
                                "studentScores": [
                                    0,
                                    2,
                                    5
                                ],
                                "studentAttempts": 3,
                                "questions": [
                                    {
                                        "options": [
                                            "a",
                                            "c",
                                            "sd",
                                            "as"
                                        ],
                                        "correctAnswer": "a",
                                        "questionText": "Enter question 1 here"
                                    },
                                    {
                                        "options": [
                                            "sa",
                                            "sd",
                                            "das",
                                            "das"
                                        ],
                                        "correctAnswer": "sa",
                                        "questionText": "Enter question 2 here"
                                    },
                                    {
                                        "options": [
                                            "ds",
                                            "sd",
                                            "sd",
                                            "sd"
                                        ],
                                        "correctAnswer": "ds",
                                        "questionText": "Enter question 3 here"
                                    },
                                    {
                                        "options": [
                                            "ds",
                                            "dsf",
                                            "df",
                                            "dff"
                                        ],
                                        "correctAnswer": "ds",
                                        "questionText": "Enter question 4 here"
                                    },
                                    {
                                        "options": [
                                            "sdf",
                                            "vf",
                                            "fr",
                                            "rg"
                                        ],
                                        "correctAnswer": "sdf",
                                        "questionText": "Enter question 5 here"
                                    }
                                ],
                                "QuizId": "Q4487_L0471",
                                "passed": true
                            },
                            "lessonId": "L0471",
                            "completed": true
                        },
                        {
                            "quiz": {
                                "studentScores": [5],
                                "studentAttempts": 1,
                                "questions": [
                                    {
                                        "options": [
                                            "qew",
                                            "eqwe",
                                            "de",
                                            "eds"
                                        ],
                                        "correctAnswer": "eqwe",
                                        "questionText": "Enter question 1 here"
                                    },
                                    {
                                        "options": [
                                            "fe",
                                            "fef",
                                            "sef",
                                            "fg"
                                        ],
                                        "correctAnswer": "sef",
                                        "questionText": "Enter question 2 here"
                                    },
                                    {
                                        "options": [
                                            "hfh",
                                            "fhg",
                                            "hg",
                                            "d"
                                        ],
                                        "correctAnswer": "fhg",
                                        "questionText": "Enter question 3 here"
                                    },
                                    {
                                        "options": [
                                            "ht",
                                            "h n",
                                            "tn",
                                            "fth"
                                        ],
                                        "correctAnswer": "tn",
                                        "questionText": "Enter question 4 here"
                                    },
                                    {
                                        "options": [
                                            "h",
                                            "hf",
                                            "fd",
                                            "df"
                                        ],
                                        "correctAnswer": "hf",
                                        "questionText": "Enter question 5 here"
                                    }
                                ],
                                "QuizId": "Q3041_L1429",
                                "passed": true
                            },
                            "lessonId": "L1429",
                            "completed": true
                        }
                    ],
                    "completed": true,
                    "courseId": "C3981"
                },
                {
                    "certificate": null,
                    "lessonQuizs": [{
                        "quiz": null,
                        "lessonId": "L8135",
                        "completed": false
                    }],
                    "completed": false,
                    "courseId": "C3221"
                },
                {
                    "certificate": null,
                    "lessonQuizs": [],
                    "completed": false,
                    "courseId": "C7102"
                }
            ],
            "role": "Student",
            "userId": "6209",
            "EnrolledCourses": [
                "C3981",
                "C3221",
                "C7102"
            ],
            "email": "yasmin@gmail.com",
            "passwordHash": "3b0bbbb98aa865230f2d6979835302ca0bfbe94463489b1f28e81145d1d505fa",
            "username": "yazo"
        }
    ],
    "Admins": [{
        "role": "Admin",
        "userId": "1234",
        "email": "ad@gmail.com",
        "passwordHash": "3b0bbbb98aa865230f2d6979835302ca0bfbe94463489b1f28e81145d1d505fa",
        "username": "Admin1234"
    }]
}